sup everyone
gamers125 here today we got special
video today today we're playing
far guys the ultimate knockout or some
now i'll let you all know I’ve
never played this before but I’ve seen
people play it people have been
requesting me to play or some i
don't know I don't give a so i
thought I would try it out what do you
say here we go here we go
this had better hurt or I'm gonna choke
a now I'm just saying i
had better not be put up with some poopy
baby oh oh this look
big
oh my I might just pull my pants before
i get to the end
oh there are a lot of people a lot
of little
look at that there's a
construction worker
I'm i'll be rooting for you
i'll be rooting for you oh
oh this is hot what the
oh we fly now we fly now
oh where's that construction what
bill
did he die
where did he go
oh
that was slippery as
oh no
that's what that's what daddy lacks no
God damn
where's that truck someone girl
where did he go
is he dead
what
i that I glitch in the floor
i glitch you the fall
come on
this sucks no
are you kidding me
I'm I'm gonna lose on round one
this sucks
this suck oh it's the
construction worker guy again what's up
he's your locker for there oh you
kidding me
oh no
come on
you can do it
look at that controller why is he going
mad what the I'm ruining for you
come on
I'm not going without you
that's why I lie
that's what's up
me and him we going places together up
in this oh what the is this
freezy peak scale the frozen hour to
reach the finish line
how the am I supposed to climb a
mountain up in this oh oh uh um
I'm not doing this I cannot do this
no
oh where's the construction working
out
where is it
i know racing to the finish line
oh what the they almost slapped my
ass
where the do I go
where do I go
get away from me what
this game should have balls in my face
stop it
this game is shooting big balls in my
face no
look at that
two big white balls in my face I cannot
get past that
are you kidding me
come on
it's over
I'm done with this I ain't getting
past this
it's over
it's over oh it's over
my way
God damn this time
look at all these in front of me
how am I supposed to beat this
come on
God damn
i hope the construction will give it
he's not he's
he's my
i hope he can make it
if me and him get out what was it all
for
that's what I'm talking about look at
that
I'm not gonna make this
how can I get through no
what the
eliminated what the let's at least
see if the construction will go through
i mean he's better than me he's better
than me
okay we're doing this again
this time we're playing as a
a a disco ball or some
here we go
oh what the is this
what is this place
this looks like I'm in a
nightclub or some up in this
i guess I picked a good time to beat
disco ball
all right let's do this everyone
let's go
oh zero gravity up to this
just like albert einstein
oh
come on
you know you don't just say what makes
me think though you know how like
classic Sonic fans and monster fans like
have like a rivalry to uh we all know
classic talk is better but there are
some like stupid little baby who
you know that would this area
remind your time that I was like getting
knocked up and and I like be like
long story short I'm not going to go
into detail but one time I shoved a hot
dog up a monastery
all right
boom
are you kidding me
we back up in the ounce alba outside
again whoa
can I go faster get out of my way
are you kidding me
is that the construction worker again
is that is that you what the
oh my God
what is he doing here
bye losers bye
bye
you
we moving on
next up is my ass
oh all this again oh
well I'm ready I'm ready to have more
white balls thrown in my face
can't get enough of that can we
oh look at that I ain't doing this
i
round two we we are round two
this is the real round two we're getting
our revenge on this mountain angry
let's go
uh-oh you're not fudging me
God damn get out my way
i don't need your waffles in my face
get out of here
no
I'm flying
that's a trap I know that
oh this place has that alba einstein
zero gravity too
boom
come on we doing this we make a good
time we make a good time
we make a good job we can do this
we gotta stop and move
stop and move stop
and move
stop and move
i I know how this place runs
oh I'm gonna be the first one there
i am good where do I go where do I go
oh what the is this
i was throwing the offer opposite way
we did it
we got all the bench on the mountain
whoa I found this nation in the ass and
made it my
this game ain't gone on
what is this button bashers
that sounds sexual
press the button the locks up to score
points and defeat your rival
i got a rival
I'm gonna beat his ass
i'll reach over a bunch get points
oh this is sexual
he took my
come on
[Music]
oh are you kidding me oh we got the
yellow buns
what if they all go to his side what am
i gonna do
stay away from me
no
what are you doing
i can't do this
no no no don't
oh
that's what that's what I'm talking
about
this is no fail
did I get that
boom
come on
come on I'm I'm one point behind all
because I didn't know this game works
you can't make this up
you can make this up come on
come on
yeah how you like that
it's over it's over
there's nothing I can do
that's not what I can do up in this
he won
he's like he's like the michael Jackson
of fargos
what can I do when you're fighting the
michael Jackson of fall guys
you missed that
i can do this
are you
eliminated elim me
me
you eliminate me tim's really for five
you can't eliminate me
what the f I fell down
why did I fall down I should be moving
forward not him he cheated